IUE-CWA Local 301; Records apap023
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1941-2001; 3
  - Report of Trustees, Special, 1977 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Reservations, 1980 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Resignations, 1970-1984 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Safety, National Safety Council Accident Facts, 1969 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Salaries and Charges, District 3 Officers, 1976-1978 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Savings and Security Program, 1973-1975; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Shop Steward, General File - (Contains: misc. materials related to the position of Shop Steward)., 1971-1979 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Stevens, AC, General File - (Contains: news clippings, certificates, brochures, Christmas Greetings. For Photographs of Stevens see Series 9.). - See also AC Stevens Interview, (Series 3, Box 3, Folder 11)., 1945-1965; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Strike, News Clippings, 1945-February 15; 1946 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Strike, News Clippings, 1946 February-1946 April (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Strike - (Contains: Memos, correspondence, news clippings)., 1965-1967 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Strike - (Contains: Memos, correspondence, news clippings)., 1969-1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Strike - (Contains: Memos, correspondence, news clippings)., 1982 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Strike, Arbitration, 1966-1984 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Strike, Bank Statements, 1969-1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Strike, Bargaining, 1966-1982 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Strike, Chip Chat, 1967-1971 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Strike, Collection Fund for Strikers, 1969-1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Strike, Contracts, 1973-1985 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Strike, Coordinated Bargaining Committee, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Strike, Coordinated Bargaining Committee, 1970; Undated (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Strike, GE Battle Plan - (See also: Strike, GE Supervisor's Battle Plan, 1971). (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Strike, GE Magazines, 1967-1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Strike, GE Monogram, 1967-1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Strike, GE Supervisor's Battle Plan, 1971 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Strike, History, Notecards, ca. 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Strike, Incentive Pay Dispute of 1964, 1960-1964 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Strike, IUE/GE Report, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Strike, IUE Local 106, Essington, Pennsylvania, 1968 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Strike, IUE Local 255, Pittsfield, Massachusetts, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Strike, IUE Local 314, Hudson, New York, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Strike, IUE Local 365, Schenectady, New York, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Strike, IUE Local 558, Utica, New York, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Strike, Knolls Atomic Power Lab Settlement and Agreement, Lodge 1921, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Strike, Local 140, AFTE, Pittsfield, Massachusetts, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Strike, Local 143, AFTE, Hudson Falls, New York, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Strike, Local Supplemental Agreements, 1964-1979 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Strike, Mailings, 1966-1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Strike, "Make Schenectady Competitive", 1964-1966 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Strike, Miscellaneous - (Contains: Memos, correspondence, associated news clippings)., 1958-1968; Undated (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Strike, News Clippings, 1962-1982; Undated (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Strike, News Releases (GE), 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Strike, Payment Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Strike, Pension Coverage, 1967-1971 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Strike, Pensions, Union Representative Plan, 1969 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Strike, Pensions, Union Representative Plan, 1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Strike, Press Releases, 1966-1967 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Strike, Schenectady News Negotiations Supplement, 1969 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Strike Unity and IUE/GE Report, 1967; 1969-1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Subscriber List, Group Package, 1984 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Subscriptions, 1984 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Tax Forms, 1964-1985 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Treasury, Jack Suarez, 1962-1978 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Trial Committee, 1966-1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Union Made Products and Services, New York State Directory, 1967-1968 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Wages, Shop Wage and Rate Adjustments, 1967-1976 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Yearbook, 1967 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - YMCA, 1984-1985 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Alcoholism Project - Material related to the Local 301 project to combat the effects of alcoholism., 1960s-1970s (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Brochures and related material - Contains: "What's Libel: A Guidebook for Local Union Editors", "Charter and By-Laws of the General Electric Company", the U.S. Department of Labor's "Important Events in American Labor History", and "The Truth About Boulwarism" by Lemuel R. Boulware., 1958-1970s (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Correspondences - Includes letters to and from John Shambo, John Martucci, Joseph Mangino and others., 1967-1980 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Publicity and Publication Seminar Material, 1968 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Accident Information, 1966-1969 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Annual Field Day Program, 1952 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Benefits Information, 1982-1989 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Benefits Information, 1990-1992; Undated (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Community Welfare Council of Schenectady County, 1967-1970 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Contract Proposal Highlights, 1966 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Dangers of Atomic Energy, 1960s (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7-8)
  - Employee Compensation Scheduals, 1986 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1976 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Foreman Hiring Guide, 1958 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - GE Annual Report, 1965-1966 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - GE Insurance Bulletins, 1967 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - GE Insurance Information, 1969 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - GE Manufacturing Time Standards, 1961 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - GE Pension Plans, 1946-1973 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - GE Pension Trust Report of Trustees, 1967 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - GE Work Practice, Procedures, and Conduct brochures, Undated (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - GE/IUE Conference Board Bargaining Goals, 1985 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - GE/IUE National Agreements, 1982-1988 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - GE/IUE Settlement Agreements, 1991-1994 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Insurance and Benefits Plans, 1950-1963 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Local 301 Annual Reports, 1944-1946 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - The Local 301 Story pamphlet, 1968 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Pension and Insurance Committee, 1969 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Preventative Medicine, 1966-1969 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Seniority Issues, 1986-1996 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Steam Turbine Policies and Instructions, 1972 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Strike Welfare Benefits, 1969-1970 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - New York State Assembly Resolution, 1993 July 17 (Oversized 8)
  - City of Schenectady Resolution, 2001 April 9 (Oversized 8)
- Audiovisual, ca. 1950-1976; 4
  Series 4 contains audio and video materials. Most of the materials relate to strikes, interviews with members of GE and IUE, and radio programs. Much of the audio contains information on the "Make Schenectady Competitive" Program.
  - Radio speech on "Make Schenectady Competitive" Plan, by Al Jandreau, business manager of IUE 301, 1964 (Reel 1)
  - Radio call-in show on "Make Schenectady Competitive" Plan, reply by A. C. Stevens of General Electric to the previous week's program, 1964 (Reel 2)
  - Radio call-in show on "Make Schenectady Competitive" Plan, with Theodore (?) Parker of General Electric and John Shambo, President of IUE Local 301, as guests, 1964 (Reel 3A)
  - Parker, General Electric representative, refusing to talk during negotiations with a tape recorder running, ca. 1964 (Reel 3B)
  - Speech on "Make Schenectady Competitive" Plan, by John Shambo, president of IUE Local 301, at the Van Curler Hotel, Schenectady, ca. 1964 (Reel 4)
  - Meeting of IUE Local 301, president John Shambo explaining the agreement concerning the "Make Schenectady Competitive" Plan, ca. 1964 (Reel 5)
  - Audio portion of a television program produced by G.E. about the "Make Schenectady Competitive" Plan, with Charles Elston, general manager of Schenectady General Electric's steam and turbine generator department, 1965 November 30 (Reel 6)
  - Hearing on Schenectady's chronic unemployment by U.S. Senate Committee on Unemployment Problems, in Council Chambers of Schenectady City Hall, ca. 1965 (Reel 7)
  - Radio talk show ("Party Line") on 1966 strike (Reel 8)
  - Speech to membership about the strike, by John Shambo, president of IUE Local 301, 1966 November 20 (Reel 9)
  - Testimonial for John Shambo, candidate for New York State Assembly, ca. 1966 (Reel 10)
  - AC Stevens Interview, 1991 (Reel 11)
  - 1966-1967 Strike, 1966 October 3-1967 January 8 (Film 1)
  - 1969 Strike, General Electric Schenectady (Film 2)
  - Breakfast (?), 1959 (Film 3)
  - Fort Edward Strike, 1960s (Film 4)
  - Front Gates of General Electric (L. Jandreau and Frank Kriss), ca. 1960s (Film 5)
  - Lynn Campaign, early 1950s (Film 6)
  - Union Christmas Party, 1975 (Film 7)
  - Union Christmas Party, 1976 (Film 8)
  - Women's Conference, early 1950s (Film 9)
- Publications, 1939-2003; 5; 854
  Series 5 is composed of publications of Local 301 including IUE-CIO News and IUE-CIO Local 301 News. The newspaper is the only consistent source for information prior to the 1960s and provides background for any history of Local 301. In these newspapers, Local 301 describes its viewpoints on negotiations with management and on other topics of interest to the union and its membership. The first issues of the newspaper are actually issues of the Electrical Workers News, the UE Local 301 newspaper. These issues date from Local 301s initial decision to join the IUE when their admission to the national union had not yet been made official. The collection includes paper, microfilm, and PDF file versions of newspapers. The PDF files are available online and were created from the microfilm copies of Local 301 publications. As there may have been gaps in the publication holdings when the microfilm was created, researchers are encouraged to also check the paper version when a PDF file is not available for individual volumes. The digitization of the Local 301 publications was funded by long-time Local 301 member Helen Quirini. This series also contains strike newspapers from 1954-1971 and 1969- 1979 and recent copies of the IUE/CWA Newsletter.
  - Electrical Union News, 1939 September 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1939 October 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1939 November 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1939 December 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1940 January 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1940 January 27
  - Electrical Union News, 1940 February 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1940 March 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1940 March 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1940 March 27
  - Electrical Union News, 1940 April 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1940 May 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1940 May 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1940 July 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1940 August 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1940 November 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1940 December 9
  - Electrical Union News, 1941 January 27
  - Electrical Union News, 1941 March 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1941 April 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1941 April 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1941 April 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1941 May 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1941 May 21
  - Electrical Union News, 1941 June 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1941 July 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1941 October 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1941 December 5
  - Electrical Union News, 1941 December 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1942 March 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1942 March 30
  - Electrical Union News, 1942 April 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1942 May 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1942 May 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1942 May 22
  - Electrical Union News, 1942 June 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1942 June 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1942 July 8
  - Electrical Union News, 1942 August 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1942 August 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1942 September 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1943 August 17
  - Electrical Union News, 1943 August 31
  - Electrical Union News, 1943 September 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1943 September 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1943 October 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1943 October 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1943 November 8
  - Electrical Union News, 1943 November 22
  - Electrical Union News, 1943 December 8
  - Electrical Union News, 1943 December 22
  - Electrical Union News, 1944 January 5
  - Electrical Union News, 1944 January 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1944 February 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1944 February 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1944 February 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1944 March 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1944 March 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1944 April 14
  - Electrical Union News, 1944 April 28
  - Electrical Union News, 1944 May 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1944 May 26
  - Electrical Union News, 1944 June 9
  - Electrical Union News, 1944 June 23
  - Electrical Union News, 1944 July 7
  - Electrical Union News, 1944 July 28
  - Electrical Union News, 1944 September 23
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 January 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 January 27
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 February 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 March 10
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 March 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 May 5
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 July 21
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 August 4
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 August 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 August 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 September 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 September 8
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 September 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 October 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 October 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 October 20
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 November 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 November 10
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 November 17
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 December 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 December 8
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 December 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1945 December 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 January 14
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 January 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 February 8
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 February 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 March 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 March 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 March 8
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 March 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 March 22
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 April 4
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 April 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 April 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 April 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 May 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 May 9
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 May 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 May 23
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 May 30
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 June 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 June 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 June 20
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 June 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 June 27
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 July 4
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 July 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 July 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 July 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 August 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 August 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 August 22
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 August 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 September 5
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 September 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 September 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 September 26
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 October 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 October 10
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 October 17
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 October 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 October 31
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 November 7
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 November 14
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 November 21
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 November 27
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 December 5
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 December 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 December 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1946 December 26
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 January 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 January 9
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 January 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 January 23
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 January 30
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 February 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 February 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 February 20
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 February 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 March 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 March 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 March 21
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 March 28
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 April 4
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 April 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 April 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 April 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 May 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 May 9
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 May 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 May 23
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 May 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 June 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 June 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 June 20
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 June 27
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 July 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 July 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 July 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 July 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 August 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 August 8
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 August 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 August 22
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 August 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 September 5
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 September 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 September 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 September 26
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 October 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 October 10
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 October 17
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 October 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 October 31
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 November 7
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 November 14
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 November 21
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 November 28
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 December 4
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 December 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 December 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1947 December 26
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 January 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 January 9
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 January 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 January 23
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 January 30
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 February 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 February 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 February 20
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 February 27
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 March 5
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 March 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 March 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 March 26
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 April 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 April 9
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 April 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 April 23
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 April 30
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 May 4
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 May 14
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 May 21
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 May 28
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 June 4
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 June 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 June 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 June 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 July 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 July 9
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 July 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 July 23
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 July 30
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 August 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 August 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 August 20
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 August 27
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 September 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 September 10
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 September 17
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 September 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 October 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 October 8
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 October 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 October 22
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 October 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 November 5
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 November 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 November 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 November 26
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 December 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 December 10
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 December 17
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 December 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1948 December 31
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 January 7
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 January 14
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 January 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 January 21
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 January 28
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 February 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 February 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 February 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 March 4
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 March 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 March 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 March 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 April 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 April 8
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 April 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 April 22
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 April 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 May 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 May 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 May 20
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 May 27
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 June 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 June 10
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 June 17
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 June 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 July 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 July 8
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 July 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 July 22
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 July 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 August 5
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 August 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 August 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 August 26
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 September 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 September 9
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 September 23
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 September 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 October 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 October 7
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 October 14
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 October 21
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 October 27
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 October 28
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 October 31
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 November 4